{
    "id": "b09111567c7649bfa4eb0aef6ce1e0ff",
    "title": "Joining Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will not come …………………….. you need me.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if…not.",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8fe6e3e44c0644e39a03a70453988481"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not go ………………………. you do.",
            "description": "Unless is a conjunction it is used before a clause without is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "without",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bed749f1d26343cca5f806defb0c86b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks …………………… her mother.",
            "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used with nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b16ef93330db47808c728a3ba900c949"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do ……………………… I say.",
            "description": "As is a conjunction it is used before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a4511ac52f14c9b85b43dd3e2c6f465"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… I received the message, I started.",
            "description": "As soon as is used to mean that one action commenced immediately after another action.",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da398db954814672a356547407cfce8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I take no more ………………………. I give.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then",
                "compared to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe760e0c87ed4adfa42347d08dee7859"
        },
        {
            "question": "Scarcely had he gone ………………………. his friends arrived.",
            "description": "Either when or before is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "201779a01f4542a395fc0702110ed404"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost not only his ticket …………………….. his passport.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "but also",
                "also"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "050948ce3fa34dafb788af3813cb679e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He washed ………………… his hands nor his mouth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9516e893de34384add612dbc803dee0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not go ……………………….. you.",
            "description": "Without is a preposition. It is used before a noun/pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "055bed04bb4a4ca89e46c5c97e5955fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He succeeded ……………………….. his hard work.",
            "description": "Because of is used before a noun/pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eb9c7f19aaaf42f7a0624ba594b6047e"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. his hard work, he could not succeed.",
            "description": "In spite of and despite are interchangeable. These words are used before a noun/pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ae4b8184e56640a4bccc7480ceb29e81"
        }
    ]
}